Guide to the John Penley Photographs and Papers TAM.501
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Photographs, circa 1980-2013; 466650
  - Police Commissioner Ray Kelly marching in St Pats parade, Steve Cannon host art opening at his legendary gallery Tribes, 1995; 466983 (Box 7, Folder 058-P)
  - Cop on ave a with 100% pure whoop ass t shirt on, Chris Flash, Fran Luck Joel Myers, Clayton Patterson, circa 1990-2000; 466982 (Box 14, Folder 059-N)
  - Cop on ave a with 100% pure whoop ass t shirt on, Chris Flash, Fran Luck Joel Myers, Clayton Patterson, circa 1990-2000; 466981 (Box 7, Folder 059-P)
  - Sex Panic show naked man speaking, circa 1990-2000; 466980 (Box 14, Folder 060-N)
  - Sex Panic show naked man speaking, circa 1990-2000; 466979 (Box 7, Folder 060-P)
  - Democratic National Convention protest Chicago Dave Dellinger, Andrew Hoffman, 1998; 466978 (Box 14, Folder 061-N)
  - Democratic National Convention protest Chicago Dave Dellinger, Andrew Hoffman, 1998; 466977 (Box 7, Folder 061-P)
  - Medical Marijuana buyers club benefit Johann Moore, Penny Arcade, Mac Mcgill, circa 1990-2000; 466976 (Box 14, Folder 062-N)
  - Medical Marijuana buyers club benefit Johann Moore, Penny Arcade, Mac Mcgill, circa 1990-2000; 466975 (Box 7, Folder 062-P)
  - Musicians, circa 1990-2000; 466974 (Box 14, Folder 063-N)
  - Musicians, circa 1990-2000; 466973 (Box 7, Folder 063-P)
  - Charas event, Roland Bolan, circa 1990-2000; 466972 (Box 14, Folder 064-N)
  - Charas event, Roland Bolan, circa 1990-2000; 466971 (Box 7, Folder 064-P)
  - Lower Manhattan together event Marguarita Lopez others, circa 1990-2000; 466970 (Box 14, Folder 065-N)
  - Lower Manhattan together event Marguarita Lopez others, circa 1990-2000; 466969 (Box 7, Folder 065-P)
  - Opening of Housing Works aids housing building on Ave D with Director Charles King others, circa 1990-2000; 466968 (Box 14, Folder 066-N)
  - Opening of Housing Works aids housing building on Ave D with Director Charles King others, circa 1990-2000; 466967 (Box 7, Folder 066-P)
  - La Plaza cultural reopening ceremony with Margurita Lopez, other politicians squatters and others, circa 1990-2000; 466966 (Box 14, Folder 067-N)
  - La Plaza cultural reopening ceremony with Margurita Lopez, other politicians squatters and others, circa 1990-2000; 466965 (Box 7, Folder 067-P)
  - Democratic National Convention protest Chicago, 1998; 466964 (Box 14, Folder 068-N)
  - Democratic National Convention protest Chicago, 1998; 466963 (Box 7, Folder 068-P)
  - NY Post drivers strike protest Norman Siegel, circa 1990-2000; 466962 (Box 14, Folder 069-N)
  - NY Post drivers strike protest Norman Siegel, circa 1990-2000; 466961 (Box 7, Folder 069-P)
  - Wigstock Chelsea Pier great colorful pix, circa 1990-2000; 466960 (Box 14, Folder 070-N)
  - Wigstock Chelsea Pier great colorful pix, circa 1990-2000; 466959 (Box 7, Folder 070-P)
  - ACT UP and Housing Works protest on Brooklyn Bridge arrests and great anti Guiliani signs lots of good stuff, circa 1990-2000; 466958 (Box 14, Folder 071-N)
  - ACT UP and Housing Works protest on Brooklyn Bridge arrests and great anti Guiliani signs lots of good stuff, circa 1990-2000; 466957 (Box 7, Folder 071-P)
  - Anti Drug War protest Chicago Democratic National Convention, circa 1990-2000; 466956 (Box 14, Folder 072-N)
  - Anti Drug War protest Chicago Democratic National Convention, circa 1990-2000; 466955 (Box 7, Folder 072-P)
  - Parks Commissioner Henry Stern opening of new dog run at Tompkins Square Park, circa 1990-2000; 466954 (Box 14, Folder 073-N)
  - Parks Commissioner Henry Stern opening of new dog run at Tompkins Square Park, circa 1990-2000; 466953 (Box 7, Folder 073-P)
  - Lynne Stewart, Stanley Cohen, Ralph Poynter state supreme court, circa 1990-2000; 466952 (Box 14, Folder 074-N)
  - Lynne Stewart, Stanley Cohen, Ralph Poynter state supreme court, circa 1990-2000; 466951 (Box 7, Folder 074-P)
  - Cooper Union Politicians event, circa 1990-2000; 466950 (Box 14, Folder 075-N)
  - Cooper Union Politicians event, circa 1990-2000; 466949 (Box 7, Folder 075-P)
  - Little soldiers LES boys group, E13 St. squatter community center party lots of squatters, 1991; 466948 (Box 14, Folder 076-N)
  - Little soldiers LES boys group, E13 St. squatter community center party lots of squatters, 1991; 466947 (Box 7, Folder 076-P)
  - Guiliani is a dope marijuana is medicine pot protest, great signs, arrests, Dennis Peron, circa 1990-2000; 466946 (Box 14, Folder 077-N)
  - Guiliani is a dope marijuana is medicine pot protest, great signs, arrests, Dennis Peron, circa 1990-2000; 466945 (Box 7, Folder 077-P)
  - Armando Perez funeral very Puerto Rican traditions etc etc Margurita Lopes, Carmen Pabon LES mother Theresa, circa 1990-2000; 466944 (Box 14, Folder 078-N)
  - Armando Perez funeral very Puerto Rican traditions etc etc Margurita Lopes, Carmen Pabon LES mother Theresa, circa 1990-2000; 466943 (Box 7, Folder 078-P)
  - Emergency Services LES accident, circa 1990-2000; 466942 (Box 14, Folder 080-N)
  - Emergency Services LES accident, circa 1990-2000; 466941 (Box 7, Folder 080-P)
  - Acapulco Mexico, 2000; 466940 (Box 14, Folder 081-N)
  - Acapulco Mexico, 2000; 466939 (Box 7, Folder 081-P)
  - Stanley Cohen Paul Direnzo with cops, circa 1990-2000; 466938 (Box 14, Folder 082-N)
  - Stanley Cohen Paul Direnzo with cops, circa 1990-2000; 466937 (Box 7, Folder 082-P)
  - Crime Scene police shoot and kill kid on Ave D, circa 1990-2000; 466936 (Box 14, Folder 083-N)
  - Crime Scene police shoot and kill kid on Ave D, circa 1990-2000; 466935 (Box 7, Folder 083-P)
  - Zipolite, Oaxaco Mex. Coco Loco, 2000; 466934 (Box 14, Folder 084-N)
  - Zipolite, Oaxaco Mex. Coco Loco, 2000; 466933 (Box 7, Folder 084-P)
  - Fisherman's kids Estachuites Mexico, circa 1990-2000; 466932 (Box 7, Folder 084-P)
  - Anti Death Penalty rally Times Square Norman Siegel, 2000; 466931 (Box 14, Folder 085-N)
  - Anti Death Penalty rally Times Square Norman Siegel, 2000; 466930 (Box 7, Folder 085-P)
  - Hotel 17 party, 2000; 466929 (Box 14, Folder 086-N)
  - Hotel 17 party, 2000; 466928 (Box 7, Folder 086-P)
  - Bread and Puppett Democratic National Convention Dave Dellinger, 1998; 466927 (Box 14, Folder 087-N)
  - Bread and Puppett Democratic National Convention Dave Dellinger, 1998; 466926 (Box 7, Folder 087-P)
  - Hotel 17 wild sex party, 2000; 466925 (Box 14, Folder 088-N)
  - Hotel 17 wild sex party, 2000; 466924 (Box 7, Folder 088-P)
  - Political funeral Act Up, circa 1990-2000; 466923 (Box 7, Folder 089-P)
  - Wigstock, Lady Bunny, Rudy Sucks written on someones ass, 2000; 466922 (Box 14, Folder 090-N)
  - Wigstock, Lady Bunny, Rudy Sucks written on someones ass, 2000; 466921 (Box 7, Folder 090-P)
  - Medical marijuana Dennis Peron, Dana Beal, circa 1990-2000; 466920 (Box 7, Folder 091-P)
  - Bob Marion in Tompkins Square Park, circa 1990-2000; 466919 (Box 7, Folder 091-P)
  - Crime Scene shooting of Second Ave deli owner, circa 1990-2000; 466918 (Box 14, Folder 092-N)
  - Crime Scene shooting of Second Ave deli owner, circa 1990-2000; 466917 (Box 7, Folder 092-P)
  - NYC tattoo convention awards, circa 1990-2000; 466916 (Box 14, Folder 093-N)
  - NYC tattoo convention awards, circa 1990-2000; 466915 (Box 7, Folder 093-P)
  - Purim celebration squatted synagogue LES, circa 1990-2000; 466914 (Box 14, Folder 094-N)
  - Purim celebration squatted synagogue LES, circa 1990-2000; 466913 (Box 7, Folder 094-P)
  - Crime scene Second Ave deli owner shooting, circa 1990-2000; 466912 (Box 14, Folder 095-N)
  - Crime scene Second Ave deli owner shooting, circa 1990-2000; 466911 (Box 7, Folder 095-P)
  - Margurita Lopez campaign rally in the projects. Photo of Lynne Stewart and Stanley Cohen, circa 1990-2000; 466910 (Box 14, Folder 096-N)
  - Margurita Lopez campaign rally in the projects. Photo of Lynne Stewart and Stanley Cohen, circa 1990-2000; 466909 (Box 7, Folder 096-P)
  - Me and Peter Levasseur on Fire Island the Pines, 2000; 466908 (Box 14, Folder 097-N)
  - Me and Peter Levasseur on Fire Island the Pines, 2000; 466907 (Box 7, Folder 097-P)
  - Housing march and event in Tompkins Square Park, LOISAIDA banner by Seth Tobocman, Margurita Lopez, Fran Luck speaking at TSP, circa 1990-2000; 466906 (Box 14, Folder 098-N)
  - Housing march and event in Tompkins Square Park, LOISAIDA banner by Seth Tobocman, Margurita Lopez, Fran Luck speaking at TSP, circa 1990-2000; 466905 (Box 8, Folder 098-P)
  - Sister Mary Kelleher longtime housing advocate at candlelight vigil, circa 1990-2000; 466904 (Box 14, Folder 099-N)
  - Sister Mary Kelleher longtime housing advocate at candlelight vigil, circa 1990-2000; 466903 (Box 8, Folder 099-P)
  - Roger Manning with guitar, circa 1990-2000; 466902 (Box 14, Folder 100-N)
  - Roger Manning with guitar, circa 1990-2000; 466901 (Box 8, Folder 100-P)
  - Crazy party, homeless men on the street, circa 1990-2000; 466900 (Box 14, Folder 101-N)
  - Crazy party, homeless men on the street, circa 1990-2000; 466899 (Box 8, Folder 101-P)
  - Rudy Guiliani at opening of family drug counseling center with cop who was shot there by drug dealers, circa 1990-2000; 466898 (Box 14, Folder 102-N)
  - Rudy Guiliani at opening of family drug counseling center with cop who was shot there by drug dealers, circa 1990-2000; 466897 (Box 8, Folder 102-P)
  - Judith Malina, Xavier Wardlaw 13 St squat community center, Armando Perez with Rolando Politti, circa 1990-2000; 466896 (Box 8, Folder 103-P)
  - Tompkins Square Park Library, circa 1990-2000; 466895 (Box 14, Folder 104-N)
  - Tompkins Square Park Library, circa 1990-2000; 466894 (Box 8, Folder 104-P)
  - Wigstock, circa 1990-2000; 466893 (Box 14, Folder 105-N)
  - Wigstock, circa 1990-2000; 466892 (Box 8, Folder 105-P)
  - Tattoo convention and protest in support of undocumented immigrants, circa 1990-2000; 466891 (Box 15, Folder 106-N)
  - Tattoo convention and protest in support of undocumented immigrants, circa 1990-2000; 466890 (Box 8, Folder 106-P)
  - William Kunstler Memorial family members his daughters Ron Kuby others, circa 1990-2000; 466889 (Box 8, Folder 107-P)
  - Margurita Lopez swearing in ceremony, circa 1990-2000; 466888 (Box 15, Folder 108-N)
  - Margurita Lopez swearing in ceremony, circa 1990-2000; 466887 (Box 8, Folder 108-P)
  - B52 bar, circa 1990-2000; 466886 (Box 8, Folder 109-P)
  - Squatter concert at the gas station Eric Drooker, Stephan Said aka Stephan Smith, circa 1990-2000; 466885 (Box 15, Folder 110-N)
  - Squatter concert at the gas station Eric Drooker, Stephan Said aka Stephan Smith, circa 1990-2000; 466884 (Box 8, Folder 110-P)
  - Father George Kuhn speaks at Act Up rally, circa 1990-2000; 466883 (Box 8, Folder 113-P)
  - Adult Education class Tompkins Square Library, circa 1990-2000; 466882 (Box 15, Folder 114-N)
  - Adult Education class Tompkins Square Library, circa 1990-2000; 466881 (Box 8, Folder 114-P)
  - Housing Works and Act Up march against Councilman Antonio Pagan, circa 1990-2000; 466880 (Box 15, Folder 115-N)
  - Housing Works and Act Up march against Councilman Antonio Pagan, circa 1990-2000; 466879 (Box 8, Folder 115-P)
  - NYC tattoo convention with shots of Coney Island historical freak show banners, circa 1990-2000; 466878 (Box 15, Folder 116-N)
  - NYC tattoo convention with shots of Coney Island historical freak show banners, circa 1990-2000; 466877 (Box 8, Folder 116-P)
  - Village Voice news box with don't catch aids sticker on it, Medical Marijuana rally City Hall Dana Beal, circa 1990-2000; 466876 (Box 15, Folder 117-N)
  - Village Voice news box with don't catch aids sticker on it, Medical Marijuana rally City Hall Dana Beal, circa 1990-2000; 466875 (Box 8, Folder 117-P)
  - Rent Control protest against Gov Pataki at South St Seaport, circa 1990-2000; 466874 (Box 15, Folder 118-N)
  - Rent Control protest against Gov Pataki at South St Seaport, circa 1990-2000; 466873 (Box 8, Folder 118-P)
  - Pot smoke in Dana Beal Dennis Peron and Jerry the peddler squat pig roast, circa 1990-2000; 466872 (Box 15, Folder 119-N)
  - Pot smoke in Dana Beal Dennis Peron and Jerry the peddler squat pig roast, circa 1990-2000; 466871 (Box 8, Folder 119-P)
  - Democratic National Convention protest Tom Hayden in Chicago, circa 1990-2000; 466870 (Box 15, Folder 120-N)
  - Democratic National Convention protest Tom Hayden in Chicago, circa 1990-2000; 466869 (Box 8, Folder 120-P)
  - Mexico Puerto Angel, circa 1990-2000; 466868 (Box 8, Folder 133-P)
  - Anti fur protest Bob Barker, circa 1990-2000; 466867 (Box 15, Folder 134-N)
  - Anti fur protest Bob Barker, circa 1990-2000; 466866 (Box 8, Folder 134-P)
  - Reclaim the Streets anti Guiliani protest, circa 1990-2000; 466865 (Box 15, Folder 135-N)
  - Reclaim the Streets anti Guiliani protest, circa 1990-2000; 466864 (Box 8, Folder 135-P)
  - Blackout Bookstore closing Brad Will takes sign down, circa 1990-2000; 466863 (Box 15, Folder 136-N)
  - Blackout Bookstore closing Brad Will takes sign down, circa 1990-2000; 466862 (Box 8, Folder 136-P)
  - Guardian Angels Curtis Sliwa with Lisa Sliwa now Lisa Evers Fox local news reporter also Councilman Antonio Pagan with Curtis Sliwa, circa 1990-2000; 466861 (Box 15, Folder 143-N)
  - Guardian Angels Curtis Sliwa with Lisa Sliwa now Lisa Evers Fox local news reporter also Councilman Antonio Pagan with Curtis Sliwa, circa 1990-2000; 466860 (Box 8, Folder 143-P)
  - Father George Kuhn with Tibetan monks Tspark, circa 1990-2000; 466859 (Box 8, Folder 145-P)
  - Nicaragua, circa 1980-1990; 466858 (Box 8, Folder 146-P)
  - Dean Johnson and Dean and the weenies band dean is bald man in dress, circa 1990-2000; 466857 (Box 8, Folder 147-P)
  - Leon, Nigaragua, 1983; 466856 (Box 8, Folder 149-P)
  - Central Park, circa 1990-2000; 466855 (Box 15, Folder 150-N)
  - Central Park, circa 1990-2000; 466854 (Box 8, Folder 150-P)
  - Nicaragua, Savannah River plant sign, Philip Berrigan, circa 1980-1990; 466853 (Box 8, Folder 151-P)
  - Liberate Washington Square park protest, Anti El Salvador death squad protest NYC, circa 1990-2000; 466852 (Box 15, Folder 152-N)
  - Liberate Washington Square park protest, Anti El Salvador death squad protest NYC, circa 1990-2000; 466851 (Box 8, Folder 152-P)
  - Taylor Meade with x wife Nozomi and her band at Cave Canem, circa 1990-2000; 466850 (Box 15, Folder 158-N)
  - Taylor Meade with x wife Nozomi and her band at Cave Canem, circa 1990-2000; 466849 (Box 8, Folder 158-P)
  - Sonny Barger riding motorcycle Hells Angels, circa 1990-2000; 466848 (Box 15, Folder 159-N)
  - Sonny Barger riding motorcycle Hells Angels, circa 1990-2000; 466847 (Box 8, Folder 159-P)
  - St Marks poetry annual New Years reading Penny Arcade, Margo Howard Howard in drag the ugliest drag queen in history, circa 1980-1990; 466846 (Box 8, Folder 160-P)
  - Nicaragua, circa 1980-1990; 466845 (Box 8, Folder 162-P)
  - Penny Arcade at medical marijuana benefit, circa 1990-2000; 466844 (Box 15, Folder 163-N)
  - Penny Arcade at medical marijuana benefit, circa 1990-2000; 466843 (Box 8, Folder 163-P)
  - High Times mag party with Keith Stroup NORML, circa 1990-2000; 466842 (Box 15, Folder 164-N)
  - High Times mag party with Keith Stroup NORML, circa 1990-2000; 466841 (Box 8, Folder 164-P)
  - Martin Sheen and Daniel Berrigan homeless protest, Koch as devil banner, circa 1990-2000; 466840 (Box 8, Folder 165-P)
  - Mohawk Indian protest, AIDS housing protest, circa 1990-2000; 466839 (Box 8, Folder 166-P)
  - Good photos. Protest after police shooting of teen on Ave D Al Sharpton, Sister Elisabeth Kelleher, Margurita Lopez, circa 1990-2000; 466838 (Box 15, Folder 168-N)
  - Good photos. Protest after police shooting of teen on Ave D Al Sharpton, Sister Elisabeth Kelleher, Margurita Lopez, circa 1990-2000; 466837 (Box 8, Folder 168-P)
  - Anti and pro Bush protesters good signs, circa 1990-2000; 466836 (Box 15, Folder 169-N)
  - Anti and pro Bush protesters good signs, circa 1990-2000; 466835 (Box 8, Folder 169-P)
  - Catholic reenactment of crucifixion of Christ Tompkins Square on Easter, circa 1990-2000; 466834 (Box 15, Folder 170-N)
  - Catholic reenactment of crucifixion of Christ Tompkins Square on Easter, circa 1990-2000; 466833 (Box 8, Folder 170-P)
  - Random shots Lower East Side, circa 1980-1990; 466832 (Box 8, Folder 172-P)
  - Feeding the homeless, circa 1990-2000; 466831 (Box 8, Folder 173-P)
  - Attorney Stanley Cohen with supporters of Hamas, circa 1990-2000; 466830 (Box 15, Folder 174-N)
  - Attorney Stanley Cohen with supporters of Hamas, circa 1990-2000; 466829 (Box 8, Folder 174-P)
  - ABC NO RIO punk rock show, Fly's mural on front of ABC good stuff, circa 1990-2000; 466828 (Box 15, Folder 175-N)
  - ABC NO RIO punk rock show, Fly's mural on front of ABC good stuff, circa 1990-2000; 466827 (Box 8, Folder 175-P)
  - Abbie Hoffman memorial with Margaret Kunstler, Johanna Lawrenson others, circa 1990-2000; 466826 (Box 15, Folder 176-N)
  - Abbie Hoffman memorial with Margaret Kunstler, Johanna Lawrenson others, circa 1990-2000; 466825 (Box 8, Folder 176-P)
  - Hare Krishna punk rock benefit, circa 1990-2000; 466824 (Box 15, Folder 177-N)
  - Hare Krishna punk rock benefit, circa 1990-2000; 466823 (Box 8, Folder 177-P)
  - CBGB punk rock show, 1990; 466822 (Box 10, Folder 257-P)
  - Jonathan Shaw legendary tattoo artist, Legs McNeil reading from his book Please Kill Me, 1990; 466821 (Box 10, Folder 258-P)
  - Zapatistas San Christobal De Las Casas Mexico, 1990; 466820 (Box 10, Folder 259-P)
  - Stop the drug war rally William Kunstler Statue of Liberty t shirt, with Dana Beal, Dhrouba Bin Wahad Black Panther and Living Theater anti death penalty play with Judith Malina, Hannon Resnikof, Garrick Beck other living theater cast, undated; 466819 (Box 10, Folder 260-P)
  - Housing Works housing facility ground breaking ceremony, circa 1990-2000; 466818 (Box 10, Folder 261-P)
  - Central Park pot and hemp rally Dhrouba Bin Wahad, circa 1990-2000; 466817 (Box 10, Folder 262-P)
  - Roller skate basketball tournament, x girlfriend Victoria Larsen, circa 1990-2000; 466816 (Box 10, Folder 263-P)
  - Acapulco Mexico, circa 1990-2000; 466815 (Box 10, Folder 264-P)
  - Al Sharpton and others at march against budget cuts, circa 1990-2000; 466814 (Box 10, Folder 266-P)
  - Stop the war on the poor rally, medical marijuana rally, circa 1990-2000; 466813 (Box 10, Folder 267-P)
  - Gay Pride, Radical Fairies, Judy Garland commemoration, ACT UP good stuff, circa 1990-2000; 466812 (Box 10, Folder 268-P)
  - Pot rally Washington Square Park, circa 1990-2000; 466811 (Box 10, Folder 269-P)
  - Tom Duane, Gay Pride, people get naked as a protest at St Patricks Cathedral, circa 1990-2000; 466810 (Box 10, Folder 270-P)
  - Sofie's bar LES, circa 1990-2000; 466809 (Box 10, Folder 271-P)
  - Joe Papp landmark dedication ceremony, circa 1990-2000; 466808 (Box 10, Folder 272-P)
  - Dykes Night Out protest against violence against lesbians, circa 1990-2000; 466807 (Box 10, Folder 273-P)
  - Protest at Rudy Guiliani speaking engagement, homeless death clock good photos, circa 1990-2000; 466806 (Box 10, Folder 274-P)
  - School Program LES, circa 1990-2000; 466805 (Box 10, Folder 275-P)
  - Henry Stern at park, Perry Masco white woman, Kid Lucky with mad cow t shirt, circa 1990-2000; 466804 (Box 10, Folder 280-P)
  - Rally to save Charas community center great stuff, circa 1990-2000; 466803 (Box 10, Folder 281-P)
  - Pot march Aron Kay, 7th annual squatters mayday, Iternity black woman speaking, circa 1990-2000; 466802 (Box 10, Folder 282-P)
  - Fire scene LES, metal jam Tompkins Square, Save community gardens meeting Paula Hewlett, circa 1990-2000; 466801 (Box 10, Folder 283-P)
  - Woman with Mumia T shirt, Ave C annual street fair Latino party, circa 1990-2000; 466800 (Box 10, Folder 284-P)
  - Palenque Mexico ruins observatory, circa 1990-2000; 466799 (Box 10, Folder 285-P)
  - Democratic convention Chicago Andrew Hoffman, circa 1990-2000; 466798 (Box 10, Folder 286-P)
  - Democratic convention Chicago one of the original Chicago 8 defendants with Dennis Peron, circa 1990-2000; 466797 (Box 10, Folder 287-P)
  - Zipolite Oaxaca Mexico, circa 1990-2000; 466796 (Box 10, Folder 288-P)
  - David Dellinger one of original Chicago 8 defendants, circa 1990-2000; 466795 (Box 10, Folder 290-P)
  - Democratic Convention NY Billioniares for Bush, Revolutionary Communist Party, circa 1990-2000; 466794 (Box 10, Folder 291-P)
  - Funeral for kid shot by police, Key Food Ave A, circa 1990-2000; 466793 (Box 10, Folder 292-P)
  - Last Free Festival at Woodstock Yasgurs farm near Bethel NY, Arlo Guthrie, Richie Havens lots of others, circa 1990-2000; 466792 (Box 10, Folder 293-P)
  - Democratic Convention Protest Chicago Ibogaine protest Rennie Davis, circa 1990-2000; 466791 (Box 10, Folder 294-P)
  - Squatter concert Tompkins Square Park, Allen Ginsberg, John the Communist, David Peel, Clayton Patterson, Chris Flash Shadow newspaper, circa 1990-2000; 466790 (Box 10, Folder 295-P)
  - St Marks Hotel, circa 1990-2000; 466789 (Box 10, Folder 296-P)
  - Billionaires For Bush, John Penley in Zipolite Oaxaca Mexico, circa 1990-2000; 466788 (Box 10, Folder 297-P)
  - Veterans for peace, Revolutionary Communist party, Mumia Jamal supporters others at Unity March Philly interesting signs visuals, circa 1990-2000; 466787 (Box 10, Folder 298-P)
  - Democratic convention NYC, Anti Clinton puppet, anti war stuff, Steve Cannon in Tribes Gallery E 3rd and C, circa 1990-2000; 466786 (Box 10, Folder 299-P)
  - Republican national convention protests Philadelphia F George Bush, circa 1990-2000; 466785 (Box 10, Folder 300-P)
  - Joan Rivers, Dana Beal, Mark Kramer, circa 1990-2000; 466784 (Box 11, Folder 301-P)
  - Seth Tobocman and parents, Barbara Robin Lee engagement party Gramercy Park Synagogue, circa 1990-2000; 466783 (Box 11, Folder 302-P)
  - Democratic Convention Chicago Ben Masel with cops, Rob McDonald with missile, circa 1990-2000; 466782 (Box 11, Folder 303-P)
  - Armando Perez funeral Charas Susan Sarandon, circa 1990-2000; 466781 (Box 11, Folder 304-P)
  - Protesters using police barricade as see saw Ave A, circa 1990-2000; 466780 (Box 11, Folder 304-P)
  - Democratic Convention NYC black bloc burning American flags, circa 1990-2000; 466779 (Box 11, Folder 305-P)
  - David Dellinger with American Indian Movement leaders Republican convention Chicago, circa 1990-2000; 466778 (Box 11, Folder 306-P)
  - Andrew Hoffman DNC Chicago, circa 1990-2000; 466777 (Box 11, Folder 307-P)
  - Congresswoman Shirly Chisolm DNC Chicago also abortion protest stuff, circa 1990-2000; 466776 (Box 11, Folder 308-P)
  - Charles King with his partner Keith Williams ? Director of Housing Works at public forum on AIDS, American Indian Movement NYC, circa 1990-2000; 466775 (Box 11, Folder 309-P)
  - Ben and Jerrys concert Central Park, American Indian Movement NYC, circa 1990-2000; 466774 (Box 11, Folder 310-P)
  - Dean Johnson and other drag queens at Webster Hall (I love these) Grady Alexis murdered by cops protest, circa 1990-2000; 466773 (Box 11, Folder 311-P)
  - Palenque ruins Mexico in Chiapas wall carvings pyramids camera was broken some are great for historical value others have red line must be cropped, circa 1990-2000; 466772 (Box 11, Folder 312-P)
  - Campaign march for councilman Antonio Pagan, LES Garden rally with puppets great pix, circa 1990-2000; 466771 (Box 11, Folder 313-P)
  - KKK march Pulaski Tenn good historical stuff especially 2 KKK they are women with hoods and confederate flag. Amazing stuff., circa 1990-2000; 466770 (Box 17, Folder 315-N)
  - KKK march Pulaski Tenn good historical stuff especially 2 KKK they are women with hoods and confederate flag. Amazing stuff., circa 1990-2000; 466769 (Box 11, Folder 315-P)
  - KKK national gathering Pulaski Tennessee, circa 1990-2000; 466768 (Box 17, Folder 316-N)